来咯 营养美味的早餐
There you go. A nice yummy breakfast.
咦 那只小妖精上哪儿去了
Hey, where's the little leprechaun?
我猜他还在穿衣打扮
Oh, I think he's still getting dressed.
我是说盒子上那只 这不是我们常吃的麦片
No, on the box. This isn't our normal cereal.
因为这是商店自营品牌[通常比较便宜]
Well, because this is the store brand,
但还是很好吃
but it's delicious.
猜怎么着 有人请我去处理一个案子
Okay, guess what. I just got an offer to handle a case.
太好了 我觉得这麦片基本就是木屑
Good, because I think this cereal is mostly sawdust.
非常棒 就是 有点复杂
It is great, it's just there's, um...slight complication.
是给"衣柜衣柜
It's for Closets, Closets...
这走势不妙啊
I don't like where this is going.
-"衣柜 -别说了
- Closets... - Don't say it.
"衣柜"公司干活
Closets.
不然你以为最后一个词会是什么
What did you think the last word might be?
米奇尔 你不能给你父亲的死对头干活呀
Mitchell, you can't work for your father's rival.
等等 为什么爷爷会有死对头
Hey, wait. Why does grandpa have a rival?
-谁知道 -因为背叛
- Oh, who knows? - Betrayal.
因为三十年前
Because 30 years ago,
你爷爷的生意伙伴
your grandfather's business partner
同时也是最好的朋友 厄尔·钱伯斯
and best friend, Earl Chambers,
偷了他装有所有客户名片的名片盒
stole his rolodex with all of his clients
自己开了公司
and started his own company
自此那一天被称为"黑色星期三的下午"
on a day that is now known as Black Wednesday Afternoon.
根本没这个叫法
Nobody calls it that.
我知道是有一些不愉快的过去
Look, I know that there's some history there,
但我们就不能翻篇吗
but can't we all just move on?
你父亲还没
Your father hasn't.
他每年在这个现称为
He still crank calls Earl every year
"黑色星期三的下午"
on the anniversary of the day
还是会给厄尔打骚扰电话
that is now known as Black Wednesday Afternoon.
我真的很需要这份工作
I really need this job.
那至少先告诉你爸爸
At least tell your dad first
免得让他承受
and spare him the pain I felt
我发现你还在米格尔店里理发时
when I found out you were still
受到的那种伤害和痛苦
getting your hair cut at Miguel's.
等等 米格尔对你做了什么来着
Wait, what did Miguel do to you again?
他给我推荐了一款给脱发人群用的洗发水 米奇尔
He recommended a shampoo for thinning hair, Mitchell.
也许我们可以用这个来固定浴室里松动的瓷砖
Maybe we can use this to fix the loose tile in the bathroom.
邓菲先生 我们能占用你一点时间吗
Hey, Mr. Dunphy, can we have just a moment of your time?
拜托 我们都认识对方多长时间了
Come on, now. How long have we known each other?
我们应该直接用名字称呼对方的
We should be on a first-name basis.
或者直接叫昵称 维他命D
Better yet, a nickname basis, Vitamin D.
听你这么说好开心
Glad to hear you say that,
因为我们需要你帮点忙
'cause, um, we have a favor to ask you.
你知道迪...
You know how Dyl--
维他命D在做自己的T恤生意吧
Vitamin D has his own t-shirt business?
我早就该猜到了
Oh, I should've seen this coming.
没问题 我愿意当你的模特
Yes, I will model for you,
但你要把底片留给我
but I'm gonna need to own the negatives.
太好了
Okay, great.
同时 我们还有点希望
Also, we were kind of hoping
能让迪兰跟我在地下室里
that Dylan could stay in the basement
小住一段时间
with me for a little while.
他想省下钱来多做一些产品
He's trying to save up to build inventory,
但房租快逼死他了
and rent is killing him.
感觉他们是每六周
It feels like they're asking for money,
跟我要一次钱
like, every six weeks.
我不知道啊
I don't know, guys.
同居可是很重要的决定啊
Moving in together, that's a big step.
只要住一小段时间
It's just for a little while.
求你了
Please?
我想只要你妈妈同意 我就同意
I guess if your mom's okay with it, I'm okay with it.
那你能帮我们问问她吗
Oh, um, and could you ask her for us?
我会试看看 但这会是我今天早上
I'll give it a shot, but it'll be the second thing
说服她的第二件事了
I've talked her into this morning,
而且她现在完全醒了 大大增加了难度
and it'll be a lot trickier now that she's fully awake.
亲爱的 你有时间吗
Hey, hon. Do you have a minute?
一小会儿 我今天上班不能迟到
Just. I can't be late to work.
我们今天要发布一款新衣柜
We are unveiling a new closet today -- the Trulhatten.
是瑞典产的 便宜 现代
It's Swedish, it's cheap, it's modern.
我们要紧握宜家[瑞典品牌]的肉丸[瑞典名吃]
We're gonna grab IKEA by the meatballs.
是这样 我刚刚在跟海莉和迪兰聊
Listen, I was talking to Haley and Dylan --
他们想问问迪兰可不可以
They want to know if he can stay
在地下室住几个星期
in the basement for a few weeks.
菲尔 我觉得这样不好啊
Oh, Phil, I think that's a bad idea.
他们是成年人了
They're adults,
而且迪兰真的有在努力
and Dylan really has been getting his act together.
这不会烦到你吗
This doesn't bother you?
我不喜欢什么事情都要经过你的同意
I don't enjoy having to get Your approval for everything,
但这是我自己决定的
but that's the deal I made.
海莉和迪兰共处一室
Haley and Dylan in her bedroom.
他们自己做出的选择
They're doing what they're doing.
我觉得我们应该开明一点
I say we be evolved about it.
好吧
Fine.
如果你真的能接受我们的宝贝女儿
If you're really okay with our precious daughter
跟她的废柴男友同居
shacking up with her ne'er-do-well boyfriend,
那就请便吧
so be it.
我就是不想让他们像我们以前那样偷偷摸摸的
I just don't want them sneaking around like we had to.
我这辈子最恐怖的经历
The scariest moment of my life
就是那次我没穿裤子
was that pantsless conversation
隔着那道两截门跟你爸谈话
I had with your dad through the dutch door.
你是有多懒啊
How lazy are you?
如果你有事跟我们说 就下楼啊
If you want to talk to us, just come downstairs.
卢克 我上大学了 都不住在那里了
Luke, I'm at college. I don't even live there anymore.
大家都很想你啦
And... you have been missed.
随意啦 我试试打老妈车里的电话
Whatever. I'll try mom in the car.
我真的得跟她说点事情
I really need to talk to her about something.
我听你说呀
I'm here for you.
怎么啦
What's wrong?
好吧 是桑杰的事情啦
Well, okay. It's Sanjay.
我觉得他在躲着我
I feel like he's been avoiding me.
是啊 他真的有在疏远我
I know. He's been really distant.
跟我说看看
Uh, tell me all about it.
别担心 你要说多久说多久
And don't worry. Take all the time you need.
他再也不好好回我短信了
Well he never really texts me back anymore.
也许我应该当面问问他
Maybe I should confront him about it?
没错 去吧
Yes! Do it!
是吧 你说得对
Yeah. You know what? You are right.
我现在就给他打电话
I'm totally going to call him right now,
我要告诉他他不能这样对我
And I'm going to tell him he can't treat me this way.
不 不
No, no, no.
不 别这样
No, no, please don't.
好吧 无所谓 我知道了
Fine, whatever. I get it.
我会给他点空间
I'll give him some more space.
你现在就可以练习
You could practice right now
稍微往你右边挪一点
and take a scootch to your right.
什么
What?
你在跟谁聊天
Who are you talking to?
我弟弟
My brother.
他好可爱
He's cute.
你好 艾丽克斯的弟弟
Hi, Alex's brother.
你好 我是卢克
Hey. I'm Luke.
你是谁
Who are you?
布蕾
Brie.
我住在走廊另一头
I live down the hall.
过来借条裙子 多谢啦 艾丽克斯
Just borrowing a dress. Thanks, Alex.
再见
Mm. Bye.
再见 卢克
Bye, Luke.
我有健身的
I-I lift weights!
什么事
Hey, what's up?
曼尼 我们现在去大学[能上大学]
Manny, you and I are going to college.
你肯定能上大学的 哥们儿
You sure are, buddy.
谁会理那个辅导员说什么
Who cares what that guidance counselor said?
我姐姐的宿舍里有个女孩
Look, there's a girl in my sister's dorm
对我超感兴趣
who's super into me,
她那个超辣的室友就交给你了
and she's got a hot roommate for you.
有多辣
How hot?
尽情地想象吧
Use your imagination.
天哪
Holy cow.
我猜她能帮我忘了卡莉
I guess it would help take my mind off of Carly.
我们要不要先约好戴什么颜色的领带
Should we talk about what color ties
免得到时候撞色了
we're gonna wear so we don't clash?
挂了
Click.
曼尼
Manny.
卡莉是谁
So, who is this Carly?
卡莉·史蒂文森 她是我的啦啦队员
Carly Stevenson. She's my cheerleader,
不过我觉得她应该不是很开心
But I don't think she's too happy about it.
你说她是你的啦啦队员是什么意思
What do you mean that she's your cheerleader?
橄榄球队的传统
It's a football tradition.
每名队员都搭配一名啦啦队员
They pair each player with a cheerleader,
她们会帮队员装饰储物柜
and then they're supposed to decorate the locker,
烤饼干 留他们喜欢的发型
bake them cookies, wear their hair the way he likes it.
大家都很喜欢
It's fun for everybody.
昨天 其他所有队员的储物柜
Yesterday, all the other players' lockers
看起来都跟新奥尔良狂欢节一样
looked like Mardi Gras Floats.
而我的储物柜什么都没有
My locker, nothing.
也许你的卡莉太忙了
Maybe your Carly's busy,
不过她肯定会为你做点什么的
but I'm sure she's gonna do something nice for you.
我记得我的啦啦队员 唐娜·德里齐奥
I remember my cheerleader, Donna Deritzio.
她忙得抽不开身 为我做了某些事
She got busy and did something nice for me,
如果你懂我意思的话
if you catch my meaning.
米奇尔 你是第一个来的
Mitchell. You're the first to arrive.
快过来 我给你弄杯饮料
Come on, I'll make you a drink.
不 老爸 我不是来参加派对的
No, Dad. I'm not here for a party.
那就好 我还以为又把谁的生日给忘了
Oh, good. I thought I forgot someone's birthday again.
我有话想跟你说说
Listen, there's something I want to talk to you about.
有人请我帮他做事
Um, I got an offer to handle a case,
可我有点担心这名客户的身份
but I'm a little worried about who it's for.
有什么问题 关于捕杀鲸鱼吗
What's the matter now? Killing whales?
钻油井 还是童工
Drilling for oil? Child labor?
我来告诉你
'cause let me tell you something.
我七岁就去给人送报纸
I had a paper route when I was 7 years old,
你知道我从中得到了什么吗
and you know what it gave me?
职业进取心以及如大力水手般的右臂肌肉
A work ethic and a right arm like popeye.
不 老爸 这个...
No, Dad, it --
我要为"衣柜衣柜衣柜...
I'd be working for Closets, Closets, Closets --
下一个词最好不是"衣柜"
Next word better not be Closets.
当然是"衣柜"
Of course it's Closets!
我被你弄糊涂了
Now I'm confused.
你说的是"衣柜衣柜衣柜衣柜"公司
Are you talking about Closets, Closets, Closets, Closets,
还是"当然是衣柜"公司
or Of Course It's Closets?
因为罗伊·卡尔森是个十分正直的人
'cause Roy Carson's a straight shooter,
只是他儿子有点不太正常
and poor guy has a son who's not quite right.
你真的想让我再说一次吗
Are you really making me say this again?
是"衣柜衣柜...
It's Closets, Closets --
你不是要为那个
You're not working for that
偷我客户名片盒的厄尔·钱伯斯工作吧
rolodex-stealing Earl Chambers!
一个短期项目 只有几周
It's just short term, a few weeks.
你知道他为什么请你吗
You know why he's doing this?!
因为我是名好律师
Because I'm a good lawyer
而且去年帮你处理过一个相似的案子
who handled a similar case for you last year.
他这么做是为了让我不爽
He's doing this to mess with me!
我是被另一名律师推荐过去的
I was referred by another lawyer.
厄尔说不定都不知道是我
I doubt Earl even knows about it.
那个名片盒里全是高级客户
That rolodex was full of A-list clients.
艾瑞克·埃斯特拉达斯 弗兰·塔肯通斯
Your Erik Estradas, your Fran Tarkentons,
莱斯利·乌戈姆斯
your Leslie Uggums.
那些都是真名吗
I'm sorry, are these real names?
记得你上次做的遗嘱认证吗 你是怎么弄砸的
What about that probate? How did you mess that up?
客户都死了
Client's dead.
你有点过分了
Okay, this is crazy.
我为什么要关心你的感受
Why am I worried about your feelings
反正你根本不在乎我的感受
when you obviously have no concern for mine?
我要接受那份工作
Y-- I'm taking that job.
这就像哈特菲尔德家的人去为麦考伊家做事
It's like a Hatfield working for a McCoy.
如果哈特菲尔德家的人真的去为麦考伊家做事
If a Hatfield ever worked for a McCoy.
也许就不会再有什么荒唐的家族夙怨了
Maybe it would've ended that ridiculous family feud.
理查德·道森
Richard Dawson!
-他也在名片盒里里 -在名片盒里里
- Also in the rolodex! - Also in the rolodex!
海莉你是不是又拿了我的手机充电器
Hailey did you take my phone chargne again?
什么
What?
我的充电器是不是在你那
Do you have my charger?!
我听不见 发短信给我
I can't hear you. Just text me.
我还想呢
I wish I could!
亲爱的 你得自己买个充电器了
I really need you to get your own charger, honey.
你们都在床上啊
Oh, you're both in the bed together.
爸爸 没关系
Dad, it's fine.
我们的房间就是你的房间 菲侠盗
Our room is your room, Philibuster.
谢谢 迪兰
Thank you, Dylan.
我只是 在找我的充电器
Uh, anyway, just, uh, looking for my charger.
抱歉 老爸 不在这里
Sorry, Dad, it's not here.
看来我要习惯没有电的日子了
Guess I'll just get used to not having any power.
卡莉
Carly?
-卡莉 -什么事
- Carly? - Yeah?
-就知道是你 -你是谁
- I thought so. - Who are you?
我是曼尼的妈妈
I am Manny's mother,
我想知道你为什么
and I want to know why
没有好好装饰他的储物柜
you haven't done a better job at decorating his locker.
因为这是个愚蠢的带有性别歧视的传统
Because it's a stupid sexist tradition.
为什么不是球员来装饰我们的储物柜
Why don't the players decorate our lockers?
你应该在当上啦啦队员前
That's a very good question you should have asked yourself
问自己这个问题
before becoming a cheerleader.
给
Here.
买点好看的东西
Buy yourself something pretty
去装饰我儿子的储物柜
and put it on my son's locker.
迪尔加多·普里契特太太
Mrs. Delgado-Pritchett,
能来一下我的办公室吗
May I please see you in my office?
我要求给曼尼换一个新的啦啦队员
Okay, I want a new cheerleader for Manny.
把年级名册拿出来 我帮他挑一个
Give me this yearbook and I'm gonna pick one for him.
不行 即便我认为那是个好主意
No. Even if I did think that was a good idea,
我也不能滥用我在学校里的职权
I'm not gonna abuse my position of power in the school.
你的办公室就是个杂物房
You share an office with a tetherball.
你还是让他顺应自然成长吧
You have to just let nature take its course,
就像我最近在网络直播上看到的那样
just like this webcam I've been watching.
现在在直播一群野生水獭
It's a live stream of wild otters.
我记不清了 它是形容矮个多毛的人
I forget, is it the small hairy men
还是形容高个没毛的人
or the tall not hairy men?
矮个多毛的 不过这些是真的水獭 你看
Small hairy, but these are actual otters. Look.
这个水獭妈妈刚刚产下双胞胎幼崽
See, this mama otter just gave birth to twins.
这个小一点的 它比较虚弱
Now, the little one, he's struggling,
但你有看到它妈妈对它溺爱了吗
but do you see the mama doting on him?
不 并没有
No, you do not.
要我说 它是个不称职的母亲
Well, if you ask me, she's being a terrible mother.
她应该用自信和鱼来填饱他的肚子
She should be filling him with confidence
就像我对曼尼做的那样
and fish like I do to Manny.
高中生活充满困难 这是人生经历的一部分
High school is difficult. It's part of the experience.
而那不是件坏事
And that's not a bad thing.
学习该如何应对沮丧
Learning how to handle disappointment
坚强地战胜困难
and overcoming adversity,
也正是我能成为今天这样的一部分原因
that's part of the reason I am where I am today.
查克 不行 这里已经没有空地了
Chuck, no. No, no, no. There's no more room in here.
我求你了 拜托
I beg you, please!
会议室在那边
Conference room is down there.
很不错
Oh, very nice.
这里是钱伯斯先生的办公室
This is Mr. Chambers' office.
他正好在 让我给你们介绍一下
Oh, he's in. Let me introduce you.
厄尔 能打扰一下吗
Earl, am I bothering you?
什么事也打扰不了我 我要上《时代》周刊了
Nothing's bothering me. I'm gonna be in Time magazine.
-《衣柜时代》周刊 -闭嘴
- Closet Time. - Shut up.
-这位是律师... -好吧
- This is the attorney... - Okay. All right, all right.
处理福勒案子的 米奇尔...
handling the Fowler case, Mitchell...
-叫我米奇尔就行 -普里契特
- Just call me Mitchell. - Pritchett.
普里契特
Pritchett?
米奇·普里契特
Mitch Pritchett.
那个狗杂种杰·普里契特的儿子吗
Son of that son of a bitch Jay Pritchett?
正是在下
Reporting for duty.
公文包也别打开了
Don't bother unpacking that briefcase.
我是不会容许普里契特家的人在我这工作
I cannot have a Pritchett hanging around here.
我这里有太多敏感信息
I got too much sensitive information
都是你老爸想要得到的
your dad would love to get his hands on.
那只是个自取外卖菜单
That was a takeout menu.
我不想让他知道我在哪吃饭
I don't want that man to know where I eat.
我来这里只是为了工作
I'm just here to do a job.
我不在乎三十年前
I don't care what happened
你和我爸之间发生了什么事
between you and my dad 30 years ago.
已经过了那么长时间了吗
Has it really been that long?
发生这件事的时候我还很小
I was little when the whole thing started.
我以前总叫您厄尔叔叔
I used to call you Uncle Earl.
我还记得 你是个可爱的孩子
I remember that. You were a cute kid.
那个魔方你拼好了吗
Hey, did you ever solve that Rubik's cube?
我拼好了三面
I got three sides.
还不赖
Not bad.
管他呢 你可以留下来了
What the hell? You can stay.
也许你在这里工作
Maybe you working here can be the beginning
可以开启我们两家关系的新篇章
of a new chapter between our two families.
这么跟你说吧 你跟你爸说
I'll tell you what, you tell your dad
如果他想握手言和 我请他吃饭
if he wants to bury the hatchet, dinner's on me.
真的吗
Oh, really?
那是当然
Absolutely.
真希望我爸能像你一样通情达理
I just wish my dad was as reasonable as you.
谢谢夸奖 快出去吧
Thank you very much. Now get out of here.
我还要拍封面呢
I got to get my cover shot.
-您的照片不会上封面 -闭嘴
- You're not on the cover. - Shut up!
你们俩来这干什么
What are you two doing here?
向处于困境的家人施以援手
Reaching out to a family member in distress.
昨天你在视频里非常沮丧
You sounded pretty upset yesterday.
所以你们就大老远地开车过来了吗
So, you drove all the way down here?
太感人了
That's so sweet.
我们来陪你了
Hey, we're here for you.
你感觉怎么样 有什么新情况吗
How are you feeling? What's new?
你朋友布蕾的房间在哪
Where's your friend Brie's room?
下楼左拐 赶紧滚
Down the hall to the left. Just go.
你有蒸汽熨斗吗
Do you have a steam iron?
因为我希望这西装...
Because I would love to give this blazer a --
宝贝
Hi, honey.
抱歉回来晚了 今天简直忙疯了
Sorry I'm so late. Work was so crazy today.
从我一进公司开始
From the moment I got there,
问题就层出不穷
it was just one problem after another.
但那都是衣柜的问题 是吧
But all just closet stuff, right?
是啊
Yeah.
迪兰的事我想向你道歉
Listen, I want to apologize about the whole Dylan thing.
我没有考虑你的处境
I wasn't taking your feelings into consideration.
我知道你看到他睡在海莉房间里
I know how uncomfortable you are
非常不舒服 所以...
with him sleeping in Haley's room, so...
我认为我们应该重新考虑一下
I think we should reconsider.
真的吗
Really?
看着我
Look at me.
这不仅是我家 也是你家
This is as much your house as it is mine.
我知道
I know that.
我们一起去赶走他
Let's go kick him out.
两位 能谈一下吗
Hey, guys. Can we talk for a second?
-什么事 -还是坐下说吧
- What's up? - Actually, let's sit down.
我们要讨论一件非常重要的事
There's something pretty important we need to discuss.
好吧
Okay, whoa.
当我发现我父亲其实
This is exactly how it started out
并不在太空里时就是这样的情境
when I found out my father wasn't really in space.
经过很周密的考虑
Anyway, um, after some careful consideration...
你母亲和我有话要说
your mother has something to say.
克莱尔 你说吧
Claire, you're up.
就在那一瞬间 我突然意识到
That was the moment I realized
是菲尔想让我把迪兰赶走
Phil wanted me to kick Dylan out
这样他就能做个很酷的父亲
so he could be the cool one.
我也可以很酷
Well, I can be cool, too.
我比酷更酷[冷] 我是严寒
I'm cooler than cool. I'm frigid.
妈妈 什么事
Mom, what is it?
我们想晚上吃披萨
We were thinking about having pizza for dinner.
克莱尔
Claire.
我知道前几天已经吃过了
I know we had it a couple of days ago,
不过我太累了不想做饭
but I'm too tired to cook.
我要去换衣服了
I'm gonna go change my clothes.
克莱尔 宝贝
Claire, um...honey.
好奇怪
That was weird.
你知道什么才叫奇怪吗
You know what's weird?
本以为你爸在月球上
Thinking your dad's on the moon,
结果却看见他在商城工作
then seeing him working at the mall.
克莱尔 刚才怎么回事
Claire, what was that?
我以为我们要赶迪兰走的
I thought we were giving Dylan the boot.
是 但是我突然发现
Yeah, but then I suddenly realized
我有点霸道了
I'm being so unfair.
你乐意迪兰住在这里
You like having Dylan here.
没错 但是
Yeah, but --
亲爱的 看着我
Honey, look at me.
这不仅是我家 也是你家
This is as much your house as mine.
是吗
It is?
赶紧去叫披萨吧
Now go order the pizza.
天黑了 他们俩差不多要上床睡觉了
It's getting late and those two are heading off to bed soon.
米奇尔 你走运了
Oh, hey, Mitchell, you're in luck.
我背上还有地方可以插刀呢
There's room for another knife in my back.
我来这是想当面告诉你
I just came here to tell you to your face
你错怪厄尔了
that you're wrong about Earl.
他这人没这么坏
He is not that bad a guy.
我见过他吃熊猫肉排
I've seen him eat a panda steak.
他是有他的问题
He is a little rough around the edges,
但是他不想再跟你斗下去了
but, look, he wants the rivalry to end.
想都别想
Never!
问题不在他
You know, he's not the problem.
在你 是你有问题
You are. You.
心胸过于狭隘
So blinded by pettiness.
别人主动握手言和 你都无动于衷
You can't even see when a man's extending an olive branch,
-反而还 我的天 -怎么了
- and -- oh, my god. - What?
我只是突然意识到任何事情都有两面
I just realized there are two sides to every story,
我又有什么资格批评你呢
and who am I to discount yours?
我们还是进屋吧 然后
We should go inside and we should --
你刚才想说什么
You were saying?
没什么 我再也不说话了
Nothing. I'm never saying anything ever again.
歌洛莉亚
Gloria?
我不是
No.
歌洛莉亚
Gloria.
是我
Yes.
彩色纸带 彩灯
Streamers, twinkle lights.
"性感曼尼"
"Sexy Manny"?
我希望这里有个好医生的电话号码
I hope there's a number to a good therapist in here.
我可没时间跟你扯这个
I don't have time for this.
这是什么
What is this?
我怎么说来着
Well, well, well.
你看看这个
Would you look at that?
我说要顺其自然 你猜怎么着
I said to leave things alone, and what do you know?
啦啦队员想通了 你是不是该承认错了
The cheerleader came through, so apology accepted.
你瞎说什么呢
What are you talking about?
她这么做是因为老娘震住她了
She did this because I scared her.
好吧 不管是我们对了还是你错了
Well, whether we were both right or just me,
关键都在于船到桥头自然直
the point is things worked themselves out,
所以我觉得我们可以回家了
so I think we can go home.
卡莉 你好
Carly, hello.
太感谢你了
Thank you so much
把曼尼的储物柜装饰得这么漂亮
for doing such a great job on Manny's locker.
我还没把装饰弄上去呢
I haven't decorated it yet.
什么 那是谁
What? But then who would --
我猜我们会一直傻傻分不清楚 所以就
Well, I guess we'll never know, so...
卡梅隆
Cameron.
好吧 是我做的
Okay, fine, I did it.
说好的要让母性的本能散发光辉呢
What happened with letting mother nature take its course
就像你电脑里那些水獭那样
like the otters in your computer?
-小的那只死掉了 -什么
- The little one's dead. - What?
那只母水獭袖手旁观
The mother, she did nothing
任由老鹰把小水獭啄烂了
while an eagle pecked it apart.
大自然太残忍了
Nature is cruel.
你帮曼尼装饰了储物柜
You decorated Manny's locker?
我装饰了八个人的
I decorated eight of them.
这传统已经濒临废灭了
This tradition's on fumes.
好了
All right.
这就是了吧
So, this is it, huh?
贼鼠的老巢
The rat's nest.
哎哟喂 你好啊 杰克·罗德
Well, well, well, aloha, Jack Lord.
我的名片盒里还有你的名片呢
I remember you from my rolodex.
太糗了 我居然被你拉进坑里了
I'm so embarrassed. I can't believe I fell for it.
最起码你最后明白了
Well, at least you finally realized
这不只是什么简单的竞争
this is not some silly rivalry.
让我把他的雪茄找出来 在我二弟上摩擦摩擦
Now let me get at his cigars so I can drag my deal across it.
好吧 我得说
Okay, I have to say,
威士忌的劲儿过去了
the scotch is starting to wear off
我重新考虑了下这个计划 老爸
and I'm having second thoughts about this plan, Dad.
还有什么好考虑的
What's there to think about?
你给我照张
You take a picture of me
我用二弟摩擦这些雪茄的照片
dragging my deal across the cigars,
等他把它们都抽完
we give him enough time to smoke them,
然后再把照片发给厄尔
and we send the photo to Earl.
首先 这样一来厄尔手上就会有一张
First of all, Earl will then have a picture of you
你脱了裤子的照片
with your pants down,
而我也会记住这个可怕的画面
and I'll have that same picture
萦绕脑中 余生难忘
in my brain for the rest of my life.
你怎么就突然开始嫌弃看别人的二弟呢
Suddenly you're squeamish about seeing another man's deal?
那个家伙耍了你 米奇尔
The man made a fool of you, Mitchell!
你说得对 我想太多了
You're right. I'm overthinking it.
放它出来吧
Whip it out.
让你二弟乖乖待在裤子里 普里契特
Keep your deal in your pants, Pritchett!
所有人都管那叫二弟吗
Okay, does everybody call it a deal?
怎么我从来没听说
How have I never heard of this?
厄尔 你这次太过分了
You've gone too far this time, Earl.
把我的家人都扯进来了
Bringing my family into this.
就是 你怎么能这样 我那么信任你
Yeah. How could you? I trusted you.
我在我爸面前替你辩护
I defended you to my father,
你却把我当傻子耍
and you made me look like a fool!
而这都是为了什么呢 衣柜吗
And all for what? Closets.
你在讽刺那个让所有人开始新的一天时
You mean the place that people start each day,
都能从里面选出一身带来自信的靓装
choosing an outfit that gives them
让他们能追求梦想的那个地方吗
the confidence to achieve their dreams?
还是说那个能让奖金室摇身一变卧室
Or that magical space that turns a bonus room
让房子成为家的那一方神奇天地
into a bedroom and a house into a home?
全赖你用了廉价的材料
Thanks to cheap materials,
你卖的衣柜把房子都变成火险区了
your closets turn a house into a fire trap!
对于那事我们选择不上诉
We pleaded no contest.
但是我们没承认有罪
That is not an admission of guilt.
你逼我的 我要把二弟喊出来
I'm doing it. I'm taking my deal out.
你想得美 起来 起来
The hell you are! Get up! Get up!
我要像碾蛋壳一样把你的头碾碎
I'll crush your skull like an egg!
他们还说本学期结束前
And they say by the end of the semester,
我们就能做基因组测序了
we'll know how to sequence a genome.
我不太懂基因组
I don't know about genomes,
不过在我爸他们家那边
but on my father's side of the family,
倒是有个花园地精[音同基因]
we do have a garden gnome.
他拿蘑菇当伞撑
He uses a mushroom as an umbrella.
曼尼 该你说了
Manny, you're up.
请允许我承认
Can I just say it's so amazing
能和你们两位待在一起真是太棒了
spending some time with you two.
我真是烦透了肤浅的
I am so sick of superficial,
以自我为宇宙中心的高中女孩
self-absorbed high-school girls.
天啊 我超讨厌高中女孩
Oh, my god, I hated high-school girls.
啦啦队员是她们中最糟的
The worst are cheerleaders.
她们以前经常嘲笑我的脊柱矫正背带
They used to make fun of me behind my back brace.
准"背"好听听这句话吧
Well, brace yourself for this.
你现在很性感
You look hot now.
曼尼 还是你上吧
Manny, you're up.
请原谅我的朋友
Forgive my friend.
你们两个实在太美了
It's just that you two are so beautiful,
有点让我们不知所措
it's a little intimidating.
好吧
Okay.
大学并不像我们预想得那样
College isn't going the way we thought.
自从来到这里 我们都还没亲过男生
Neither of us has kissed a guy since we got here.
所以...
So...
你是指我们吗
You mean us?
-是的 -现在吗
- Yeah. - Now?
根据校园规定
In accordance with campus regulations,
你们已经获得我们的许可了
you have our consent.
好棒
Yes!
谢谢 我马上回来
Thank you. I'll be right back.
口香糖 口香糖 我需要口香糖
Gum, gum, gum. I need gum.
我没有
I don't have any.
谢谢
Thanks.
我终于联系上桑杰了
I finally got through to Sanjay.
这是隐私吧
Sounds personal.
我可不想打探你的隐...
I don't want to stick my nose into your --
他跟我分手了
He broke up with me.
他跟别人好上了
He's seeing someone else.
你现在应该很想一个人待着吧
Um, you probably want to be alone right now.
我已经成一个人了
I am alone.
别这样
Come on.
你会好起来的
You'll be okay.
那...
That's, uh...
我也只会用这句安慰人了
That's really all I got.
卢克 快点
Luke, hurry up.
她们快要恢复理智了
They're starting to come to their senses.
去吧 我没事
Go. It's fine.
我还是留下来陪着艾丽克斯吧
I'm gonna stay with Alex.
有什么我能做的吗
Is there anything I can do?
我觉得没有
I don't think so.
好了 为我祈祷吧
Okay, pray for me.
好了 你到家了
Well, there you are.
虽然并未如我们所愿
Didn't quite work out like we planned,
但我还是用订书机钉了他的头
but I did get that staple in his head.
你必须明白我之前的想法是出于正确的理由
You have to understand I did it for the right reasons.
我 我本只是为了我的家人
I was -- I was just looking out for my family,
但是 你也是我的家人
but... you're my family, too.
你知道今晚最棒的一点是什么吗
You know what the best part of tonight was?
并非是我一个人与厄尔对抗
It wasn't just me against Earl.
是我们一起对付他
It was us against him.
我喜欢这样
I liked that.
我也喜欢 真的
I did too. Yeah.
不过我保证 我以后再也不会站在别人那边了
And I promise I will never side with anyone else ever again.
当然了 除非你是错的
Unless, of course, you're wrong,
我还是要坚持我的基本原则
'cause I still do have my principles.
好吧
Okay.
下车吧
Just get out of the car.
走之前我得给你这个
First I have to give you this.
是我那个名片盒
It's my old rolodex!
没错 我从他办公室偷出来的
Yeah. I stole it out of his office.
怎么可能 什么时候偷的
But how? When?
你们俩在那张办公桌上扭打了大约十分钟吧
You guys were rolling around under that desk for about 10 minutes.
我拿走以后 还有时间回复邮件呢
After I grabbed it, I had time to return some e-mails.
谢谢你
Thank you for this.
它很有意义[二弟]
It's a huge deal.
对我而言这个词已经被污染了
That word's kind of tainted for me now, so...
你们冷吗 我可以把温度调高点
You guys cold? I can turn up the heat,
你们就用不着披毯子了
get you out from underneath that blanket.
不用了 菲邓[洛杉矶警局]
We're good, L.A.P.D.
尽管我很想把迪兰赶出去 但我是不会退缩的
As bad as I wanted Dylan out, I wasn't gonna flinch.
这事必须由菲尔来做
Phil needed to do it.
他必须得跟网上那只鹰一样强硬
He needed to be as tough as that eagle on the internet.
那只愚蠢的水獭完全没料到它的突袭
Dumb otter never saw it coming.
打住啦 好痒啊
Oh, stop! That tickles!
你还好吗 菲尔
You all right, Phil?
好得很 正享受电影呢
Yeah, just enjoying the movie.
你喜欢这片吗 根本不恐怖啊
Oh, you are? It's not even scary.
那是我见过的最傻的海怪了
Like, that is the lamest sea monster I've ever seen.
那是因为你能看得到
That's 'cause you can see it.
如果你能想象表面[毯子]之下
It is way scarier if you can only imagine
发生着些什么 那就可怕多了
what's going on beneath the surface.
够了 我受够了
That's it! I'm done!
海莉 迪兰
Haley, Dylan,
你们这个同居小方案
this little living arrangement of yours,
是行不通的 必须改改了
It's not working out and it's about to change.
老爸 你急个什么劲儿啊
Dad, why are you freaking out?
因为我是你父亲
Because I'm your father
我无法容忍你们俩
and I can't have the two of you
睡在一个屋子里 却假装这没什么大不了的
sleeping together in the same room like it's no big deal.
所以 从现在起
So, from now on,
你们必须对我表现出应有的尊重
you're gonna show me the respect I deserve
背着我偷偷摸摸地干这些事
and sneak around behind my back.
干什么事
Do what, now?
我不明白
I don't understand.
从今晚开始 你睡艾丽克斯的屋子里
Starting tonight, you're sleeping in Alex's room,
如果你们要耍什么花招
And if there's any monkey business,
最好趁我睡着了以后再搞
better happen after I'm asleep.
你开什么玩笑啊
Are you serious?!
-我可以接受 -我也是
- I'm okay with that. - Me too.
我不能接受
I'm not okay with that.
我任何一点都不能接受
I'm not okay with any of that.
海莉 你必须把重点放在工作上
Haley, you need to start focusing on your job.
迪兰 你明天就得搬出去
Dylan, you're moving out tomorrow.
到此为止
End of discussion!
抱歉 我不是酷妈
Sorry. I'm not the cool mom.
绝不是酷妈
Not the cool mom.
孩子们 我尽力了
Hey, guys, I tried.
谢了
Thanks.
你跑我床上来干什么
What are you doing in my bed?!
等着你爸睡着啊
Waiting for your dad to fall asleep.
怎么回事啊
What is going on in here?!
艾丽克斯 你怎么回来了
Alex, why are you home?
桑杰跟我分手了
Sanjay broke up with me.
小宝贝
Sweetheart.
一切都会好起来的
Everything will be fine.
滚去跟海莉睡吧
Just go sleep with Hayley.